<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Courses on xBurrito&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://xburrito.github.io/course/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Courses on xBurrito&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 13:15:02 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xburrito.github.io/course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 13:15:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course4/</guid>
      <description>Course Code: Csc 22000 Langauges used: Python Topics covered within this curriculum:
 Algorithms and Problems:  sorting algorithms bubblesort insertion sort Randomized Algorithms Quicksort Divide-and-Conquer Mergesort Analysis of Recursions   Data Structures  Heapsort   Others  Radix Sort Binary search trees: Find, Insert, Delete, Rotate Spanning Trees Rebalancing algorithms Graph analysis: Depth first search (DFS) and Breadth first search (BFS) Shortest path: Dijkstra&amp;rsquo;s Algorithm Dynamic programming algorithms     O-Notation: Focused mainly on time and space complexity when running through algorithms Analysis of Expected Runtime: We calculate each algorithm&amp;rsquo;s Big-O to determine the most efficient algorithms when handling problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Structures</title>
      <link>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 13:15:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course1/</guid>
      <description>Course Code: Csc 21200 Langauges used: C++ In this course, I have gone over the basics of data structures.
Linked Lists Description: We covered the functionality of pointers and nodes in order to construct linked lists which could be dynamically resized unlike predefined arrays. On top of constructing a linked list, we gone over appending a node to the head, tail, or anywhere within the linked list.
Stacks Description: Stacks follow last in, first out (LIFO) procedures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Processing</title>
      <link>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 13:15:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course5/</guid>
      <description>Course Code: Csc 47000 Langauges used: C++ This course involves using compression based algorithms alongside A.I. to modify image samples as well as reverse the process back to the original state or even aim to improve its original quality. The topics covered throughout the course:
 Ability to implement point operations such as:  thresholding quantization gamma correction histogram manipulation halftoning implement neighborhood operations such as:  blurring sharpening convolution     Knowledge of image reconstruction, re-sampling and antialiasing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operating Systems</title>
      <link>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 13:15:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course3/</guid>
      <description>Course Code: Csc 33200 Langauges used: C, C++, Java Topics covered throughout the semester both in class and in lab:
 Types of Operating Systems I/O Structure Storage Structure and Storage Hierarchy Operating System Services Process Scheduling Algorithms Inter Process Communication Dead Lock and Dead Lock Prevention and Avoidance Paging, Segmentation, Paging with Segmentation Virtual Memory File Concepts File Accessing methods Memory Management  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Design</title>
      <link>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 13:15:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xburrito.github.io/course/course2/</guid>
      <description>Course Code: Csc 22100 Langauges used: Java In this course, we worked towards understanding key topics such as when working through each lab assignment:
  Public/Private Classes
  Setters/Getters
  Abstract and Interface class
  Description: This contains methods within the class without showing you what is under the hood. The methods could be called and expected to perform as intended when provided the right parameteres, if any.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
